Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high.
Hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky.
Time to journey on.
On your mark.
Camel of other things.
We're on Earth, a legendary.
Hooray!
If you can show your breath,
Then we'll make some waves.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners.
Cause if you're wanted,
Then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise,
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day.
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece.
I'll be the first.
I've heard it be so fast.
I could burst.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel.
I'm done playing, filled with the waiting.
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind.
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed.
I'm done playing through with the wave.
In every world I'm feeling alive.
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
Meanwhile, at Candy Factory Town,
in the center of the island.
Bostama?
Hey, are you okay?
He's chewing right
through the factory walls.
Yeah, like he was nothing.
My fangs eat for long.
What's this crap?
I don't want some trendy cappuccino latte
thing or fancy sponge
cake when I'm hungry.
That junk's not real food.
What in the hell do I look like?
I'm sorry, boss.
I'll get something else.
That's good, because you're starting
to look pretty tasty yourself.
For a snack, I like fish
bones, and I like them big.
Now, go!
Oh, sure thing. Big fish bones. I got it.
Never mind.
I'm going to go whimp my appetite on some
soldiers and maybe the Ryo family, too.
Guess I'll see the rest of
you bums at Conchcord Plaza.
Don't you dare be late.
We all have to be there.
What should we do about
the citizens? Come on.
Did you morons pay attention
to a word Captain Horde said?
He told us, no more
stepping on her picture.
Leave him alone for now.
Those losers will get what's
coming to them soon enough.
Yeah, yeah.
How are we supposed to
stand up to these guys?
Including Heart, the new Fishman pirates
have Horshark Fishman as officers.
And a giant squidfishman.
Not to mention their bodyguard
is a blue-ringed octopus
merman known as the best
swordsman on the entire island.
I think the Neptune brothers are
the only hope we've got left.
Then all we can do is keep the faith.
At Waterwheel Town in the
island's northern region.
Did you hear?
The princes are making
their way to Concord Plaza.
This country's in such a mess.
Tell me about it.
All we wanted to do was improve
our relationship with the humans.
There's no reason to threaten everyone
with death like some kind of madman.
And on top of those threats,
they want to execute the king.
Maybe Heart will be
willing to bargain with us.
After all, we've got his men held hostage.
Your plan isn't going to work.
Boss Heart would rather you
cut us Downson than negotiate.
He's more ruthless than
the other fishman pirates.
That's why he looks
Downson on the rest of us.
This can't be good.
Ever since the prince has defeated him,
Officer Dosan's power level
has dropped to Downson.
Now he's just weak and gloomy.
Let me give him an energy steroid.
Thinking about it just brings
me Downson. It's depressing.
Heart doesn't like fishmen who
do business with human pirates.
He'll give them the Bumson without mercy.
Bumson?
All those fishmen who donated their
blood to help out wounded humans?
He gave them the old Whompson
in the dark of night. Whompson?
Hardy believes that human
blood is naturally tainted.
And whenever we receive their
blood or offer them our own,
we dose in our pure blood under service!
He's back to saying docent now.
Any fishman who supports humans is
a traitor and needs to be punished.
Our people will never be able
to advance with them in our way.
All right, that's enough.
I'm gonna go whamson on you!
He's higher than thousand!
The chains are shattered!
You bastard!
They knocked him out with
one swing! Mukabushi!
I'll get you back with a slant, son!
Then I'll smash your face
with a big, fat boom, son!
My enemies will face doom, son!
Hit the Cunchcord Plaza for
the execution! Let's move!
At the south part of the island, in
front of the Fishman Cultural Hall,
Huh?
Oh, you call it drunk.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
It's me.
This isn't funny anymore, boss!
Pull yourself together.
You're in no shape to fight like that.
I think you worry too much, pal. Relax.
Drinks are on the house.
It's my treat.
That's not important right now.
Fukaboshi is leading
Neptune's army into the plaza.
We have to be ready for them.
Even worse, if things go bad,
Jinbei might even show up to fight.
This isn't a joke, boss!
It's no use!
He's weak as a sea cucumber
and just as slippery!
Huh?
How about me?
How'd you get your head
spinning around like that?
Ugh, I'm standing still!
How drunk are you? This is awful!
I doubt Yasuie can even hold his sword!
Sure I can.
Get away from him immediately!
I'm serious!
Yasuie will slice into anyone and
everyone when he's this drunk!
Make a run for it!
You slice anyone.
He attacked his own guys.
See, I can fight just fine.
Right, boys!
Hey, Yasuie, why don't
you go to the plaza?
There you can cut up the royal
family as much as you want.
Huh?
I, uh, know why, uh, nah What?
What is that even supposed to mean?
At the marine shopping mall in
the east part of the island?
You think you pathetic civilian stand
a chance you're dumber than I thought!
Beach can blend in perfectly with the
surroundings to camouflage himself.
Just like a chameleon
He might be on our side,
but even we have trouble
figuring out where he is
What this is unfair how are we supposed
to fight someone we can't even see?
You might as well start begging for
the Neptune brothers to bail you out?
Without them you're finished!
Though frankly don't expect
them to last long either.
Oh well time to finish you
Did we get it is it dead?
Yeah, we got it
You fools have nowhere to run it's only a
matter of time before
we hunt you all down?
There's no escaping our
wrath he's talking like
nothing happened we
just beat him to a boat!
What class no wonder he's called
the noble of the fishman district?
Prepare for the revolution.
Later on today, at Conchcord Plaza.
The Neptune family will die,
and a new king will rise.
Now, let's head to the execution.
How much longer before
we arrive at the plaza?
Less than an hour, sir!
Executing the king at Conchcord
Plaza feels calculated.
Why not just do it at the palace?
I think Heart might be trying
to lure you princes into a trap.
That is no concern to me.
I look forward to this fight.
I will not let them murder our father.
And I refuse to let our citizens'
hearts and minds become closed
off after all we've worked for.
Jinbei kept Heart under his watchful eye,
and now I see that we should
have taken note of that.
He's probably the reason human pirates
have stopped coming here as well,
an issue we should have
investigated sooner.
Sandy, do you think Shirahoshi
is still in the hardshell tower?
We haven't heard anything
about Sis in a while,
and it's really starting
to bug Mayfassola!
How did you feel about the Straw Hats?
Because I didn't think
they were bad people.
Madam Charlie said that
they destroyed the country,
but so far they seem like
the least of our worries.
They have caused their share of
trouble, but they may be victims too.
That's what I think.
Straw Hats G-Mae's friend, and the
mermaids didn't have a problem with them.
And frankly, their
judgment is really wrong.
Agreed, but this is not the time nor
the place to ponder such questions.
Right!
We need to focus, Solatido!
Summon every soldier that
the country has to offer!
We're going to save our
king at any cost! Yes, sir!
At Fishfilly Hills in the
northeast part of the island...
It's too tough! Damn it,
we shouldn't be having this much trouble
fighting against just one sea monster!
But then again, it seems
something is amiss!
The energy steroids are making him crazy!
Hey, calm down, sea bear. That's enough.
The soldiers are barely alive.
Our job here is done.
Use this.
Sea kings don't like fire. Stay back!
What the I don't think his arms are
supposed to bend back like that.
He must be under some kind of a curse
you idiot put out that fire right away!
Sakehi!
Hot, hot, hot! Huh?
He said something about fire? Fire!
What are you trying to do?
Cook up some smoked squid?
You think we'd eat you?
Oh, the fire.
You were trying to roast me and
have me with a glass of sake, he.
When I recover, I'll kill you.
Who'd want to do that?
You're crazy!
Oh, sorry, sir.
Careful.
I heard about how one of Ikoros'
best friends was a giant squid.
One day, he swam too close to the sun.
Before you know it, he
was a giant dried squid.
That's why Icarus freaks
out when he sees fire.
I'm sorry, Dinolos!
But if he's a fish man, he doesn't
have anything to worry about.
Dinol!
No more fire! Got me here! Oh no!
That dried squid spear is dangerous.
It turns back into a normal squid by sucking
all the fluid out of anyone it strikes.
That guy's as good as jerky.
Icarus.
Wow, that's rough.
First he got dried out
and then this happened?
Okay, boss Icarus, I
think he's had enough.
Isn't it about time we start
making our way to Conchcord Plaza?
We're here.
You're right.
It's too late for that
guy. Leave him here.
Minister!
You need to see this, sir!
Heart!
Is that him up there?
I don't see Heart, but I do see
other men from the Fishman District!
They must be heading
for the Conchcord Plaza!
Damn those bastards!
No way!
They still have King Neptune hostage!
You can't let them beat you!
Please do something!
Great night!
You people need you!
I'm no great knight. Not anymore.
Look at me.
I can't even save my poor citizens.
Please hang in there.
What good is a king's army if it
can't even protect the king it serves?
We're an embarrassment to this country.
Siricaros, just two hours
left to the execution.
Come with us to Conchcord Plaza.
What happened to Captain Heart?
Is he not with you?
Why isn't he talking to me directly here?
How about that?
That drug enhances your strength
at the cost of your lifespan.
You shouldn't have taken
it in the first place.
Shut up.
Captain Heart was injured.
The human pirate swordsman cut him
in the gashes too painful to bear.
Injured?
The captain got injured?
His body wouldn't stop hurting,
so he kept taking energy
steroids to help kill the pain.
Now he's messed up.
We told him to stop, but he
wouldn't listen to anyone.
Oh, Captain Head!
I can't breathe.
I can't...
I feel like I'm gonna explode.
It's just as I suspected.
The drug side effects are
bad enough to kill you.
What's wrong with you now, Sea Bear?
I think he must be afraid.
But all these Sea Monsters have been under
Captain Forty's control
for a really long time.
I don't know what would spook him so much.
Come on, Captain.
Quit blubbering.
Yeah, things will start looking up soon.
Just get back in the game.
Like I would ever take advice
from a couple of losers like you.
You guys have no idea what it's
like having your heart broken.
These feelings are real.
I've wanted her since
I first saw her. Sure,
she was just a kid,
but I knew if I married her, I
could fulfill my ancestor's dream.
But what happened instead?
You're just not my type! No!
Not my type, she said.
When the words came to my
ears, I felt my love grow.
A flawless haiku by Vandertick
in the night, I suspect!
My soul?
It's aching!
After she rejected me, I felt like it
was time for a change, so I cut my hair
I just attacked!
I thought I'd kill her instead,
but I can't even get that right.
I know she's alive because I
can still throw things at her!
This is not Straw Hat's fault!
Wait, that's it?
What's so funny? My idea!
If I can't end her existence, then
I'll just have to end everyone else's!
It's gonna be great!
You'll see!
NEPOSAL
No!
Neptune's Army is done for!
Every last one!
They didn't stand a chance.
The party is too strong.
We are all done for!
Minister of the Right!
Minister of the Left!
We couldn't do anything.
We were so close.
You're going to be okay.
After so long.
Please stay with us.
We were finally supposed to see results.
This was going to be our
year at the World Summit.
Queen Otohime.
But then they had to come and ruin
everything someone help us save the
king if we don't stop them soon he will
be executed surely someone can fight
we can't get in they locked the
entrance to the plaza behind them
kingdom tune let's scale the wall
maybe we can see inside Hide!
Thank you.
Let us make haste, Megalo!
I thought you soldiers were
supposed to protect this country!
My men!
Damn you, Heart!
Look alive, boys.
That soldier's up to something.
You think so?
Looks like he's packing dynamite!
He's gonna blow everyone up with
some kind of suicide attack!
But if he does that, I'm
gonna turn into roasted squid!
The three princes should get here soon.
But I can take out at least
one of you before they do.
Oh no, look out!
Water shot.
How far can it go?!
You hear that?
That whistling sound! What is it?
Oh, my God.
Am I crazy?
I was under the impression the
water shot wasn't that strong.
I know it took a lot of energy
steroid to get that tough, but still,
that was incredible!
We never anticipated it changing your hair
color or increasing your
muscle mass so greatly,
though.
How are you feeling, Captain?
Couldn't be better.
What happened here?
Why didn't the soldiers
wait for us to have them?
Fukaboshi, Ryoboshi, Mamboshi.
Don't underestimate them.
Both their ranks and their sea
monsters have been empowered by a drug.
Now it makes sense.
On an even playing field, Neptune's
army would never lose a sortie.
No!
It's time to mumble. Ready?
Why don't you understand
you're all so pathetic
you new fishman pirates are
just a bunch of cowards!
The other islanders let go of their hurt
feelings brought on by
the humans discrimination!
And despite the fact that
humans murdered their
hero and their queen
they're willing to forgive!
Them even after all of
their suffering they still
sign their names because
they want to change the?
future.
Your highness.
Wait for the Beach.
What you do undermines their efforts.
Can't
you recognize their bravery?
You're kidding me, right?
Don't mistake their kindness for courage.
He gives the humans another
excuse to take advantage of us.
you seek revenge not for
justice but because of your
own personal hatred I won't
let you take the king's life,
nor the island his citizens call home.
You will never have the Ryugu kingdom!
We're saved!
We should have known we
could count on the princes!
We will never be defeated, because we've
been granted a power that is absolute.
And with that power we will rule this
country the way it was always meant to be.
The future of this country is peace,
peace with the humans and peace
with that monsters like you.
If we don't triumph here
we'll have failed and
it will be hundreds of
years before we have.
Another shot at friendship
with the human world.
Oh is that a fact?
Well then the winners of this
fight will rule this country. Ray.
They look... stronger!
What? But how?
Too slow.
Time is running short, little old.
Be safe, Father.
We'll be there soon.
He's going to be fine.
I promise you, Princess.
Thank you.